He's got it. He's got it.
Nasic!
Come here, boy.
Well, and then he says that I'm
lactose intolerant
and I'm like: "dude you have no clue."
Of course you are lactose intolerant.
I've been eating cheese all my life.
Yeah, and that's why you sit on
the loo for so long.
Hey, Isaac
I saw Franzi with a new guy.
Yeah, after three weeks.
Do you know what I would do
to be able to fuck around
like you again.
Doesn't Moni let you have it anymore,
or what?
Since the little one arrived - here...
I could do with a change.
No, thanks.
She even calls him by the
same nickname as me.
And which one?
Doesn't matter.
Isaac, Franzi wasn't
the brightest anyway, huh.
But those legs dude.
It's funny. I mean
we were together for a year.
Every day and then
three weeks.
As if nothing had ever happened.
Do you want her to slit her wrists
from being love sick?
Fuck you, ok.
My turn.
Let's go Grinsi.
Hello, good evening.
What can I do for you?
Seven beers and chasers
plus an alcohol-free.
Where do you want it to go?
What lane are you playing on?
- 14.
I'll bring it right away.
- Just a moment, ok.
- Thank you.
Excuse me?
We ordered some drinks.
Where?
With whom?
- With your colleague.
- What do you get?
Two gin tonic.
I'll bring them when I'm finished
with this gentleman.
- We've been waiting since forever.
- Yes, but he was...
Make the drinks for the ladies first.
Ok.
One moment.
I'll be right back.
Thank you.
Your friend doesn't look like
she's enjoying herself.
She's not really into bowling.
Why don't you join us?
Those idiots will make her laugh.
Rather difficult with my sister.
I can be very charming.
I bet.
And there are your two gin and tonic.
That's 9.80 euro please.
Hey, what's up?
I got it.
- Can you bring them over?
- Right away.
No, I told you we will...
I'll do that.
Can you bring them to the table?
- I will.
- Thank you.
No, I told you it won't
work like that.
And who are you?
Isaac.
You don't have to entertain
me to please Ilona.
Don't you want to have fun?
I'm having fun.
What's your name?
Edith.
That's a nice watch.
Doesn't work anymore.
Any watch is right twice a day.
What?
That's not what I meant.
They say that even a broken watch
is right twice a day.
That's what I meant.
You can have it.
Will take a while with Ilona.
Cheers.
I don't drink.
Why?
I don't take it so well.
But then you'll play a round with us.
- One round.
- No, thank you.
One round.
Goodbye.
- Oh, shit.
- Are you stupid? Fuck off, man.
- Yo, what's up with that?
- Hey!
- Can't you watch out?
- Can't you see, dude?
Man, why do you push me like that?
Don't you see that she is
in a wheelchair?
Beat it dude.
You fucking soldiers.
- I didn't know. I swear.
- Then open your eyes the next time.
You must believe me.
I didn't know.
Really.
Leave me alone, ok.
I didn't know.
I swear.
Just open your eyes.
Look.
Stop staring.
Man, what's your problem? Really...
- That was so unnecessary.
- I didn't know.
I didn't know!
Why are you filming?
Put it away!
I didn't know.
Hey, hey.
- All good, ok.
- Yeah...
Take...
How am I supposed to know
that she's disabled?
- Here, take a sip.
- What?
Should she wear a sign next time?
That's the daughter of
Schwartz you've chosen.
Who is that?
Amazing. Cool.
The guy owns everything here.
I'm out.
No, no, no, Nasic.
We'll party a bit longer.
- Don't be like that, boy.
- It's all good.
Don't touch me!
Don't touch me.
- Hey, chill.
- Fuck! Fuck!
- Awesome.
- Shut up, Grinsi.
Leave it.
Ok, guys.
Here's the second thing.
A lot of people will say:
"Hey, how's work these days?"
I've always felt that's
a really terrible question.
It's just going to give
a one word answer.
And, let's be honest...
Most people don't even
like their work.
Ask them something
they want to talk about.
Let's say: "Hey, what's exciting
about your work right now?"
So, you're pushing them
where they want to go.
Can't you see that she's
in a wheelchair?
Move dude.
I didn't know.
You fucking soldiers.
Calm down.
You must believe me. I...
This girl in the chair...
I wanted her to play with us.
Because I didn't see the chair.
Ah, a chair.
Yes, a wheelchair. Yes.
What?
But if you didn't know,
it cannot be your fault.
Mum...
But she didn't fall off the
chair by herself.
Okay, so what are you trying to say?
That these things only
ever happen to me.
That's classic me.
IMPATIENCE OF THE HEART
What are you doing here?
I wanted to apologize to your sister.
One moment.
Hi.
Bad conscience?
I mean, I couldn't see the wheelchair.
So it's my fault.
- Of course not.
- Well, thank God.
Did you hurt yourself?
Nothing I could feel.
Why do you go bowling if you
can't even play?
Why don't you fly having
ears like that?
Hey, I'm really not that
kind of a guy.
- Ready?
- What for?
- Well, for the lake.
- I can't get through the sand anyway.
Then we don't go all the
way to the shore.
I don't have to go to the lake if
I can't go swimming.
We had a deal...
What do I care about my
chatter from yesterday?
I can help you.
No, thank you.
That would be great.
Come, it's really nice.
Later.
Once you're in, you'll love it.
- I swear.
- I just said: "later".
Please Eddie. Please, please, please.
Just go on your own.
Edith?
- Hi.
Hi, I'm Charlie.
- I'm Ilona.
- We did our A-levels together.
Long time no see.
- How are you?
- Great.
Hey, Steff and the others
are all back there.
Hm.
Cool.
Why don't you come over?
We were just about to go for a swim.
We have prosecco on ice.
The heat is really bad for me.
- Oh.
- Mhm.
Thank you for coming over.
We might come over later.
Bye.
Oh, that's far too cold.
Want to get on the air mattress?
You could swim a bit first.
It's so cold, I'll get spasms.
Since when do you get spasms?
I think she was quite nice.
I never liked that princess
and now she's acting like
we're best friends.
You really make it a bit
difficult sometimes, Eddie.
Please stay a bit closer to the shore.
Bye.
What are you doing?
You're such an asshole!
Hello.
Hey Mark, what's going on?
I thought it was all set.
I think this is the longest time
I've ever seen Ilona without a
phone to her ear.
What does she do?
Consulting.
I see.
Do you do proper motocross?
What do you mean with proper?
Ah, with jumping and all that?
Yes, with jumping and all that.
Meaning competitions.
No, I just like the bike.
And you want to be a bit
like Ryan Gosling.
This is actually almost exactly the
bike from the movie.
Yes, probably couldn't
afford a DRZ 400.
Shit, you're all red.
What?
Mark, I'll call you back.
You should have gone to the
toilet before we left.
- Shit, I forgot the catheters...
- Ilona!
Ah, hi.
What are you still doing here?
I'm waiting for your sister.
She's in a call.
May take a while.
Shit.
Is there a bus around here?
What about your bike?
It won't start.
- But you've filled it up, right?
- Yes, of course.
I just did a check-up.
I bet 5 euro it's the spark plug.
How do you know so much about it?
What are you trying to say?
- I'm just asking.
- Yeah, me too.
Is this your room?
No, my room is upstairs.
It's just easier here at the moment.
At the moment?
Mhm...
Why, is that...
I mean, is this even curable?
Why not?
They also grow an ear on the back
of a lab rat and sew it back onto you.
I used to ride motocross myself.
- Really?
- Mhm.
Were you any good?
- Quite.
- Hello!
Hello!
Dad, here.
Is Doro here?
No, I cancelled on her.
Eddie...
Daddy...
Who's bike is it then?
Ah, I didn't see you there.
Hey!
Dad, you don't know him.
This is a buddy of Ilonas.
- Oh, ok.
- Isaac Nasic. Nice to meet you.
You were looking forward to the
weekend with Doro so much.
No Dad. You were looking forward
to a weekend without me.
- Edith...
- Someone has to get Isaac home.
Why, what's wrong with your bike?
It won't start.
And now?
Ilona wanted to give me a ride.
Where is she?
- Call...
- Ah.
Do you want to borrow that one?
No, thank you.
Where do you live?
Paradise settlement.
Ah, we built that one as well.
I'll drive you to the bus.
No, please don't.
Don't bother.
The car is still outside anyway.
Don't keep him waiting.
What's this for?
I have no idea.
How do you know Ilona?
Are you a school friend of hers?
I'm deployed here.
Deployed?
A soldier?
Yes.
I wouldn't have guessed that.
May I ask why?
I...
I want to give something
back to my country.
Ha...
My father was also in the army.
He was killed in Afghanistan.
Explosive device in front of an
elementary school.
On the site of the former
military training area,
in a central but quiet location
five residential buildings are
being constructed
to a worth of 44 million Euro.
Owner Schwartz, who had set up a
foundation for breast cancer
in memory of his late wife
two months ago,
was delighted with the numerous guests
at the laying of the foundation stone.
Torchbearer.
March!
Stand still!
Torchbearer, right and left.
Turn!
Grand parade.
Adjust!
Blood supply to your cock.
Hard as fuck.
As long as you want.
- No way.
- Absolutely. As long as you want.
Does that mean you get a boner
by pushing a button?
You'll get hard by pushing a button,
bro.
And you'll cum. Once, twice...
No matter what. It stays up.
People already have that?
There is already a fucking test.
There is a small chance that
everything will get inflamed.
But if things go well,
you can get hard whenever you want.
But if you don't want a boner...
you can also push a button
and it will go down.
End-of-service beer at the lake today?
I'll catch up with you.
- What you catch up?
- Why catch up, man?
I have to take care of something.
Of what?
My bike.
Yeah right.
You're going to fuck that
Schwartz lady again.
- Don't move.
- Bring her along.
I'd love to see her in a bikini.
Hey.
Ilona is in a call.
I was about to leave anyway.
Come on.
Wait.
Yes!
Ok, great.
What did I say?
Where is your bike?
My father sold it.
Why is that?
Well, it's not possible anymore.
Oh, can you take that?
My hands are fully covered with oil.
Hello?
Who's this?
Edith.
So it's Grinsi.
They want to know where you are.
Tell them it will take some more time.
He says it will take a bit longer,
okay?
Someone is in the lake.
And something with eucalyptus candy.
Who says you can no
longer ride a bike?
I mean you can still sit.
You want to tell me what I
can and can't do?
Did you try it?
No.
Do you want to?
I mean, what could possibly go wrong?
Okay, wait a minute. I have
to lift the stand.
Clutch.
Of course HR whines about
something like that.
You're all acting like babies.
Shit. What are they doing there?
I'll call you back.
Cut the crap.
Slow.
Edith.
Eddie.
Eddie, are you?
Lift the bike.
Everything ok?
- Yes.
- Yes?
Let's have a look.
Did you see me?
Torchbearer.
Stop!
Torchbearer, right and left. Turn!
Torchbearer. Attention!
Raise the rifle!
Today we want to march.
Try a new march.
In the beautiful Westerwald.
Where the wind whistles so cold.
Oh, you beautiful Westerwald.
Eucalyptus candy!
The wind whistles so cold
over your caves.
But the smallest ray of sun
goes deep into the heart.
- May I?
- Yes, of course.
Tell me, Holzer, have you
shaved your penis,
so that Moni will suck you again?
It's too late for that, bro.
But it looks bigger now.
Hello, Isaac.
This is your father speaking.
I heard you're in the army now...
Well, maybe you'll pull this one
through for a change.
Ah, and happy birthday.
Mr. Schwartz.
Hello Isaac.
Hello.
The girls are not here.
Ah.
Nobody tells me anything either.
What is that?
It's a stairlift.
One company delivers,
the other installs.
And they just leave it like that?
Well...
- Do you have a minute?
- Sure.
Be careful, it's heavy.
That's okay.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What kind of a question is that?
Edith has the same one, right?
No, but it's similar.
My wife gave it to her for
her 18th birthday.
I had to work hard for mine.
I was thinking about letting my
contract with the army expire.
Ah. Really?
And what do you want to do then?
- What did you think I was doing?
- What do you mean?
You were so surprised that I
was in the army.
When?
When you were driving me home.
Ah...
I mean, what did you learn?
You didn't study anything, right?
Not everyone has the possibilities.
You have a special effect on people,
Isaac.
I've heard that before.
But it wasn't always well-intentioned.
Want to try it on?
- That's okay.
- Come on. Put it on.
Here, take it.
Always above a table.
Mhm.
Do you know how you can tell
that it's a real one?
No. Here.
Can you hear?
Beautiful.
Ahhh!
What the fuck is that?!
Get rid of that immediately!
Eddie, please.
What the fuck, Dad?
Get rid of it!
Get rid of it. Get rid of it now!
Edith.
We need to get a grip on
things at some point.
I can't always be at home
and Ilona also has a life in Berlin.
If I'm such a burden, then send me to
one of those institutions.
Edith, that's not the point.
It can't go on like this forever.
Fuck off, Dad!
Fuck off, ok.
Come on, I'll help you.
And you too.
Go away.
Please Eddie.
I want to be alone.
Please go.
I don't need a fucking
wheelchair lift.
I got it.
What are you doing here?
Visiting you.
Where do you want to go?
To my room.
Where is that?
All the way up.
That could get exhausting.
Funny.
Shall I?
Yes.
Hold on tight, ok.
Ok.
Where to?
Onto the bed.
Will you go there with me?
It's all mud there.
I won't get through it with the chair.
I'll carry you.
That would make me uncomfortable.
Then I'll tie you to the bike.
I'm taking my wife to the riviera.
Ciao, ciao, basta.
Ciao. Dolce vita.
The whole thing.
And I was left alone with the company.
Here are the keys, take
over the business.
You're better at it anyways...
Back then we maybe had 50, 60 trucks.
Just like back then.
It's always all down to me.
Well, my daughters don't want to
take over the company.
Oh god.
Never, Dad.
I've told you, that I could imagine it.
But that's not even your area.
It is exactly my area.
What do you think I'm doing?
I go into companies, analyse their
structures and improve them.
There is no need to improve
our structures.
I am the structure.
- Whatever.
- Have a look.
Doro just send me that.
Who is Doro?
- My motocross friend.
- Are you sure you don't want any?
Thank you.
- Who is that?
- He's also paralysed.
- Wow.
- Heavy.
It's a bit scary.
Come on, nothing could ever stop
you from anything.
Edith has always been the
courageous one in this house.
You know what?
I'll buy you one of those.
You can't buy something like that.
You have to strip a bike and
weld on the brackets.
Aha, and can you do that?
Sure.
You could actually open a
motorcycle store.
I already have a job.
Well...
Do you want to do this forever?
Yes.
You're so incredibly
arrogant sometimes.
What's wrong with her?
What's wrong with you?
Hi.
You okay?
Are you leaving?
I wanted to look for
motorcycles with Edith.
Okay.
Your dad is quite something.
I think he's really proud of you.
Well aren't you cute.
I have another call now, but
do you want to meet in the shed
and fuck afterwards?
What now?
Yes, okay.
Okay.
Thank you.
That's a good one.
It's perfect. Hardly any panelling.
Let me see.
How did you actually get
into motocross?
No one else in your family does that,
right?
I don't know either.
It already fascinated me as a child.
Sorry about what I said
about the army.
Dad just told me about your father.
That's okay.
My mother died when I was twelve.
I'm sorry.
How old were you?
What?
14.
What kind of unit are you actually in?
Guard Battalion.
What do you do there?
Primarily protocol honour service.
What is that?
We're at state receptions
and stuff like that.
Actually a bit...
...pointless.
So why are you doing it?
The discipline does me good.
Says who?
Me.
But it doesn't seem to be
your dream job.
So what would you do if
money wouldn't matter?
Hm.
Where did you learn this?
My father...
...wasn't actually in Afghanistan.
He is not even a soldier.
He just left us behind.
Then why do you tell stuff like that?
You're lucky to have such a great dad.
Boo!
Hey.
Woof!
Aaah-oo.
Finally Nasic.
Eckner, you've got
something in your hair.
I have something everywhere.
I'll probably find something in
my panties tomorrow.
Nasic.
You have so much potential.
You just need to focus a
little better.
Focus, exactly.
You have to stay on top of things.
You and I.
We have to be a unit.
Wait a minute, didn't they arrive
with a BMW the other day?
My Golf is still faster.
- Really?
- Save.
Dude...
They have three cars.
The insurance alone would bankrupt me.
What's wrong with you?
Come on, give me a hand.
Ok, chill dude.
Hello.
Ok, hold on tight.
1,2,3.
Up.
Hi.
How are you?
Good, and you?
Good.
Do you want to join us?
We have no time.
Takes about ten minutes.
- Name?
- Edith.
This is Ben.
Claudi.
Hi.
Holzer.
And this is Grinsi.
My brother-in-law is
also a consultant.
Really? Where?
Well I always forget the
name of the company.
Hm.
And...
...you two are friends now, or
what's the set up?
Yes.
Edith used to ride motocross.
You are truly inspiring.
What do you mean by that?
Because I was riding
motocross as a woman,
or because I eat fries as a
disabled person?
That's not what I meant.
Edith.
He only means well.
Yeah.
Well, you know what would be nice?
Asking a woman in a wheelchair before
you drag her somewhere.
- Bitch.
- Are you going to carry me out or not?
But that still doesn't give her the
right to be such a bitch.
- True.
- If I was as underfucked as her...
I'd be pretty bitchy too.
As if you get laid much.
Well, more than her.
But more than zero is still
not much Grinsi.
Maybe 0.3.
Sex with 0.3 people.
How is that supposed to work?
Torso porn, dude.
No arms, no legs.
Eww. Such a thing exists?
Of course.
It would be perfect for her.
Someone like that couldn't
run away from her.
Woah, guys...
I'm out.
What?
Come on, we're just messing around.
- Nasic!
- Yeah, all good.
When you came on stage and said you
wanted to be like Sam Smith
everyone laughed at you.
And look, now nobody is
laughing anymore.
Your performance was incredible.
For me, that's definitely a "Yes".
I think Edith fancies me.
Edith?
I thought you were
fucking the other one.
My boy. Nasic!
Did he still cry a lot?
No, he was just tired.
Moni...
A girl in a wheelchair has fallen
in love with Isaac.
Why do you always have to
flirt with everyone?
I wasn't flirting with her.
She's like a little sister to me.
Aha.
What do you mean by "aha"?
Then why did she fall in
love with you?
- I don't know.
- Take a look at this gorgeous boy.
Mum!
Hey, I couldn't do it with
one of those either.
It's not a problem for me that
she's in a wheelchair.
I'm just not into her.
What can I do about it?
So why are you hanging out with
her in the first place?
Hey!
- Schmitti!
- Hi.
Did we just miss you?
No, I'm about to go.
Hi.
- Isaac.
- I'm Doro.
Is The Krüger also on?
No, she's injured.
Then you'll finally have a
chance of winning.
I think you have to go.
Yeah... Hey.
- Good luck.
- Thank you. Bye, take care.
- Bye.
Fuck! I want to do that too.
The way you're driving, it's
still a long way to go.
What do you mean?
You drive like a grandma.
I was only careful because you were
sitting on the back.
Yeah, sure.
Look at him, look at him!
Thank you for persuading me.
It's nice to see you so happy.
Sometimes I wished that I had
died in the accident.
Hey.
You can't say that.
I feel completely at the mercy of
others without the chair.
Do you want to go home?
Yes.
Can you turn around?
Come on.
I'll do it.
Be aware, they look funny.
Not at all.
They are getting thinner every day.
Hey...
Did I hurt you?
No.
But I just don't want you
to look at my ass.
Okay.
Can't we just do it normal?
Yes, of course.
It's so cold.
There is this therapy.
With stem cells.
A few paralyzed people can
walk again as a result of it.
Really?
Mhm.
The chances aren't exactly high.
And...
I think the side effects
are pretty bad.
But if there is a possibility
to be able to walk again, one
has to do it, no?
What are those side effects?
I'm a fighter.
May I?
Is there something going
on between you?
What now?
Yes, so what?
Is this some kind of revenge because I
don't want to be your girlfriend?
No.
Are you after my dad's money?
What the fuck?
So you're a couple now, or what?
I mean, I don't have to marry
her straight away.
Are you in love with her?
- I like her.
- So you're not. Okay.
Listen to me.
If you're not serious about her
then you have to tell her.
Okay?
Hello?
Mhm.
May I please go now?
Here.
That's my old one.
- It's for you.
- I can't accept that.
Why not?
Thank you very much.
But I've always earned
everything by myself.
Please do me the favour.
You're embarrassing him, dad.
But why?
There's nothing to it.
Eddie, why don't you say something?
I have a surgery appointment.
- Which surgery?
- Stem cell therapy in Poland.
I have nothing to do with that.
I'm glad you're happy for me, Dad.
It's no joke, Eddie.
We've talked about this.
- I know.
- Then get it out of your head.
The doctor said that in my case there
is a 20% chance of...
I don't want to hear anything
about it anymore.
Let her speak at least.
Stay out of this.
So 20%?
Where did they get those numbers?
- Is this their own study, or...
- It is my body.
And how are you going to pay for it?
Health insurance won't cover it.
- I'll take Mom's inheritance.
- I manage that.
- It belongs to...
- Enough!
How much does such a therapy cost?
21.000 euro.
I'll borrow it to you.
I've brought you some snacks.
Where did you get that much money from?
I took out a loan.
Here.
What?
You can have it.
He won't miss it.
What the fuck?
I was wrong about your father.
Hey, did I wake you up?
That's okay.
Can I get you anything?
Mm.
Okay...
I'll be back at 5:30pm.
Your father is back in
two hours anyway.
Okay.
Oh, em...
And later I have to go to Holzers.
Is that okay?
You can do whatever you want.
I'm really not in the mood,
but it's his birthday.
So why are you doing it?
You wouldn't understand
It's camaraderie.
Explain it to me.
I don't have time for that.
Okay, so first you think
it's all ridiculous,
and now you're acting like it's a
matter of life and death.
What am I supposed to do?
I have made a commitment.
Build up something else.
You've got more to offer
than those morons.
Hey, they are my friends.
You don't even know them.
Then go.
- Go!
- Edith...
No leave, I want to be alone anyway.
- Even a really old picture.
- Grinsi...
- Don't you spot something like that?
- Well, I...
Look at this thing.
Wow, can I see?
- Oh, that's really heavy.
- Hey.
Let me see.
- Are you a couple now?
- With whom?
- With that Schwartz girl.
- Seems to pay off.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing.
I bought it myself.
Mhm.
And the picture?
That was a stupid bet.
Hm.
No chatting.
Continue.
When did you stop telling me things?
Nasic?
There's a lot going on right now.
Mhm.
Are you coming tonight?
Yes, of course.
Why don't you bring Edith?
I don't think that she is
into stuff like that.
Hey!
Yeah?
Come with me.
Why do you think I am
against this therapy?
- We were informed about the risks.
- Really?
So tell me, which stem cells do
they use for the oligodendrocytes?
Do you know that?
I don't know that right now.
Do you know how high the tumour risk is
with such an allogeneic transplant?
You're pushing Edith into such
a therapy and you
and you haven't even properly
informed yourself?
You don't know Edith.
You have to protect her from
herself sometimes.
You're underestimating
Edith right now.
Dad?
Dad!
Hey.
What happened?
I lost my balance somehow.
Can you help me?
Yes, of course.
- How?
- Here.
Have you been sick again?
I'm fine again.
Can you pass me the bathrobe?
Sure.
Do you really want to go
through with this?
What?
Well, with the therapy.
What's a bit of vomiting if I
could walk again.
Well that's not all.
Are you backing out?
No.
I thought you were on my side.
I am.
Are you ashamed of me?
What the fuck is that about?
Then why don't you take me to Holzers?
Why?
Do you want to?
No.
But I want you to ask me.
Oh.
Alright... Prosecco?
I'm not allowed right now.
Thank you.
Oh God.
How are you going to put up
with it here then?
Nasic!
Come on, line up.
- Look what you're doing!
- Come on now!
Hey.
You little guy.
Mum, TV.
Excuse me?
I didn't understand you.
Dear mum, can you please turn on
the TV for me, please?
I'll be right there.
He is so sweet.
A little devil.
But he can be quite sweet
when he wants to be.
I used to work for your father.
Oh.
That's not what I meant.
Don't worry.
Mum!
I'll be right back.
Otherwise we'll never have any peace.
Oh, sorry.
Why are you always
sitting in that chair?
Because my legs are broken.
Why?
Because I had an accident.
Because someone wasn't
paying attention.
Are you sad?
Sometimes.
Do you want to watch with me?
I'd love to.
Tommy.
Go to your mum.
It's okay.
- But I've only just started.
- Go.
No!
It's really okay.
Or I'll turn it off.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
He's such a sweet boy.
Are we not good enough for you?
Not at all.
- I wanted...
- Holzer!
1,2,3,4.
Today we want to march.
Try a new march.
In the beautiful Westerwald.
Where the wind whistles so cold.
Holzer!
Oh, you beautiful Westerwald.
Eucalyptus candy!
The wind whistles so cold
over your caves.
However, the smallest sunshine
goes deep into your heart.
Yes!
Thank you.
Thank you, you fuckers.
Holzer old bastard, make a speech!
We even have a star guest
among us today.
A real Schwartz.
I am honoured that a real Schwartz
is here with us today.
Let's hear it!
- He doesn't mean it in a bad way.
- Yes, and she also brought her nurse.
So thank you for
having made it all the way to my
modest little hut.
- Now, the important things.
- Hey!
Hey!
- What the fuck?
- Apologize to her now.
Right now. Apologize to her!
It was just a joke.
Immediately!
You apologize to her.
It was really just a joke.
Shut up!
What kind of people are you?
Do you think it's normal to punch
someone in the face like that?
What was I supposed to do?
Just look the other way, or what?
You shouldn't drink.
I don't recognize you anymore.
Sorry.
What's going on in here?
I know.
I want to be better for you.
Are you working late again tomorrow?
Why?
Tomorrow is the second
round in Poland.
That's already tomorrow?
It's okay.
- Ilona will drive me.
- No, no, no. I'll do that.
I'll drive you.
You're still not done.
How stupid can one actually be?
Is Private Holzer supposed to
help you or what?
Tell me, what did you actually
learn in kindergarten?
Is that supposed to be
refined motor skills?
I don't want to know what a mess
it is when you pee!
- Don't shout at me.
- What?!
Please don't shout at me.
Do you think you can ask everyone to
be quiet on the battle field
so that you can assemble
your rifle in peace?
The guard battalion does not
fight in any battle.
A real smart ass...
The whole unit. Up!
Get down!
Push-ups!
Not you Nasic.
You will assemble your
fucking rifle now.
Everyone else. Go!
Hey.
- What's wrong?
- Everything is okay.
- That doesn't sound good at all.
- That's normal.
- How is that normal?
- Wait, wait.
She wants to be alone.
Eddie?
Open up!
Do you want to eat something?
Mm.
No food.
I'll prepare something and then I have
to go. Okay?
Dad comes back tomorrow morning.
You look beautiful.
Call me anytime.
Look, I filmed this in the clinic.
What is that?
Look.
He is also paraplegic?
Imagine...
Who are you trying to
prove something to?
I'm only trying to help.
You all let her down.
What did you just say?
Who do you think you are?
You know nothing about our live.
Nothing.
Just leave us alone.
This family...
treats her...
They gave up already.
And they treat me like
I'm the bad guy.
Like the bad guy...
The bad guy?
Why?
Maybe because they are so arrogant.
They feel guilty because they have
already given up on her.
And you want to stay?
Mum, the girl only has me.
She needs me.
Nobody believes in her.
Only I.
This girl only has me.
And what about work?
About work?
What?
I just don't want you to
get your hopes up.
Are you for real?
How do you want to achieve anything
with such an attitude?
- Where do you get those lines from?
- Don't talk to him like that.
How do I talk?
As if he was stupid.
He's not exactly a doctor, is he?
Well, are you one?
Me? No.
I'm not a doctor.
But I have spoken to all the leading
neurologists in this field.
And they all happened to tell
me the same thing.
- All of them!
- Ah.
Eddie...
Sorry!
Ahh.
Did you just feel that?
I think so.
Yes!
A little, light sting.
And that?
Do you feel that too?
No.
- Okay, but you just felt something.
- Yes!
Yes!
Okay.
- 20%...
- How is that possible?
20%!
- Ms. Schwartz.
- Hello.
Hello.
How are you?
That depends on what you are
about to tell me now.
Unfortunately, I don't have any
good news for you.
The therapy did not work as we hoped.
That cannot be.
I felt something in my
legs this morning.
That can't be related to the therapy.
Your body did not accept
the stem cells.
What is your plan now?
What do you suggest?
For now you should try to recover from
the exhausting therapy.
I'll simply take more of
those blockers.
Could her body still accept
the stem cells?
How did you react to the pills so far?
She is tough.
First you have to gain
your strength back.
So you're just giving up on me?
We'll take another pack
of the blockers.
I'm done Isaac.
You heard the doctor.
You just need to take a little bit
more of those blockers.
Your body can still accept
the stem cells.
It's pointless.
You are so naive.
You are so naive sometimes.
What kind of shitty
mentality is that?!
I thought you were a fighter.
Show them what you're made of.
Who is that?
Dad.
Mute him.
Hey!
You know what he's going
to say anyways.
Shit.
Shit!
Did they see us?
What's going on?
I was absent from duty
without authorization.
What does that mean?
That I'm fucked.
Are they following us?
- Sorry.
- Fuck!
Sorry.
Shit.
Okay.
Here are the tablets and a bucket in
case you have to throw up again.
I have to go and solve this
thing with the army.
Mhm.
What are you doing here?
- They're looking for you everywhere.
- I know.
What's wrong with you?
Dude, Edith is not feeling well.
Move. Move.
Where is Edith?
- She just laid down to rest.
- Why aren't you answering the phone?
Everything is under control.
How is she?
What did the doctor say?
We have to keep going a bit.
Just a bit longer.
There hasn't been a breakthrough yet,
but...
- Every day this will get worse!
- Man, just shut up!
Edith!
Spit it out!
Edith.
Shit.
I am such a fuck-up.
Here.
Sleep a bit.
Mr. Schwartz!
Wait!
- Hello Isaac.
- How is Edith?
She was lucky.
Okay.
Can I go see her?
She needs to rest.
Okay.
Then I'll come back later.
No, that's not possible.
Why not?
She doesn't want to see
you anymore Isaac.
She said that?
Yes.
Mr. Schwartz, please.
I have to see her.
I don't have anything else.
Please.
I love Edith.
Hi.
That was quite something...
I thought a lot, helps a lot.
I shouldn't have pushed you like that.
Isaac, I won't be able to walk again.
Not tomorrow, not the day
after tomorrow.
If you want to stop the therapy, we
will stop it immediately.
Done. Okay?
Done.
You don't have to do that.
What are you saying?
Edith, I love you.
Will you marry me?
I'm serious.
As soon as you feel better,
we'll go to the jeweller
and I'll buy you a ring.
You've spent all your money
on the therapy.
If we don't make the second round,
I'll still have enough.
You might have to make
a few compromises.
Maybe it will only be a small one.
The apartment we will be able to
afford in the beginning
won't be that big either, but
I'm going to open the
motorcycle store.
You can write a book.
You have so much to tell.
And with this money we will
buy a house in Italy.
I have a visitor.
Okay.
You'd better go now.
Did I say something wrong?
Yes, I'm looking forward too...
Let's see, I think she
still has a visitor.
Where is Isaac?
Gone.
Ok.
Was he just here?